[Waco] Daughters of the American Revolution: Henry Downs Chapter records, Inclusive: 1897-2006, undated, Bulk: 1960-1990
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Minutes, 1930-1991; 3
  - Minutes: General: Henry Downs Chapter, 1986 March-November (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Minutes: General: Henry Downs Chapter, 1986 December-1987 September (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Minutes: General: Henry Downs Chapter, 1987 October-1988 March (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Minutes: General: Henry Downs Chapter, 1988 April-1989 March (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Minutes: General: Henry Downs Chapter, 1989 April-1990 January (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Minutes: General: Henry Downs Chapter, 1990 February-April (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Minutes: General: Henry Downs Chapter, 1990 May-November (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Minutes: General: Henry Downs Chapter, 1990 December-1991 March (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Minutes: General: Henry Downs Chapter, 1991 April-May (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Minutes: Notebook: Henry Downs Chapter: (1 of 12), 1978-1981 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Minutes: Notebook: Henry Downs Chapter: (2 of 12), 1978-1981 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Minutes: Notebook: Henry Downs Chapter: (3 of 12), 1978-1981 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Minutes: Notebook: Henry Downs Chapter: (4 of 12), 1978-1981 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Minutes: Notebook: Henry Downs Chapter: (5 of 12), 1978-1981 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Minutes: Notebook: Henry Downs Chapter: (6 of 12), 1978-1981 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Minutes: Notebook: Henry Downs Chapter: (7 of 12), 1978-1981 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Minutes: Notebook: Henry Downs Chapter: (8 of 12), 1978-1981 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Minutes: Notebook: Henry Downs Chapter: (9 of 12), 1978-1981 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Minutes: Notebook: Henry Downs Chapter: (10 of 12), 1978-1981 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Minutes: Notebook: Henry Downs Chapter: (11 of 12), 1978-1981 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Minutes: Notebook: Henry Downs Chapter: (12 of 12), 1978-1981 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Minutes: Proceedings: Annual Conferences: Texas Society Daughters of the American Revolution, 1943, 1944, 1955, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Minutes: Proceedings: Eighty-Fourth Annual Conference: Texas Society Daughters of the American Revolution, 1983 March 13-15 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Applications, 1897-2003; 4
  The following series contains the application forms submitted by those women who sought membership in the Henry Downs Chapter of the Daughters of the American Revolution. These materials are particularly important for the genealogist, because each member was required to prove one’s relationship to a Revolutionary War veteran. The materials are in average to good condition.
  - Membership: General, 1975-1989 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Membership: Index, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Membership: Regents, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Membership: Abbott-Allen, 1911-1984 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Membership: Aman-Armstrong, 1922-1996 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Membership: Armstrong-Arth, 1938-1999 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Membership: Atkinson-Austin, 1924-1935 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Membership: Auten, 1991-1994 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Membership: Autry-Azbell, 1923-1982 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Membership: Bain-Baldwin, 1923-1988 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Membership: Ball-Barnhart, 1923-1986 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Membership: Barrett-Bates, 1927-2000 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Membership: Batson-Belew, 1901-2003 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Membership: Benedict-Bennett, 1910-1985 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Membership: Bennett-Bertling, 1939-2001 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Membership: Bessire-Boggess, 1908-1996 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Membership: Boiles-Bracken, 1897-1988 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Membership: Bradford-Brooks, 1924-1995 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Membership: Brooks-Brown, 1940-1997 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Membership: Brown-Bryan, 1951-1990 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Membership: Bryant-Bunn, 1973-1986 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Membership: Burbridge-Burrows, 1918-2000 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Membership: Butler-Byrd, 1928-1977 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Membership: Caffee-Cameron, 1921-1989 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Membership: Campbell-Carney, 1910-1989 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Membership: Carns-Cash, 1901-1996 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Membership: Caskey-Cates, 1928-2003 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Membership: Cates-Chandler, 1980-2001 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Membership: Chapman-Christman, 1927-1990 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Membership: Clair-Clark, 1981-1989 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Membership: Clark-Clayton, 1916-1984 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Membership: Clayton-Clement, 1926-1982 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Membership: Clifton-Colgin, 1918-1990 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Membership: Coleman-Colemere, 1931-1981 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Membership: Collins-Cook, 1917-1982 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Membership: Cook-Craven, 1907-1997 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Membership: Cravens-Cutbirth, 1924-2003 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Membership: Dancer-Davis, 1913-1993 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Membership: Day-Dillard, 1928-1983 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Membership: Dilworth-Dollins, 1900-1977 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Membership: Donaldson-Dossett, 1903-1980 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Membership: Dotson-Duncan, 1914-1976 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Membership: Dunham-Durham, 1907-1990 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Membership: Early-Edwards, 1911-2002 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Membership: Eidson-Erwin, 1973-1986 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Membership: Evans-Ewing, 1903-1951 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Membership: Fair-Ferguson, 1919-2002 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Membership: Ferguson-Fitzhugh, 1926-1982 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Membership: Fitzpatrick-Folley, 1924-1988 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Membership: Fontaine-Franklin, 1924-1995 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Membership: Franklin-Fugate, 1967-1995 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Membership: Gannon-Garrison, 1901-1981 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Membership: Geelon-Gething, 1939-1978 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Membership: Gholson-Gilchrist, 1959-1983 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Membership: Gildersleeve-Gladdish, 1920-1996 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Membership: Glasco-Gorman, 1922-1989 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Membership: Grace-Graves, 1946-1996 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Membership: Greene-Griffin, 1924-1988 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Membership: Griffith-Guinn, 1921-1991 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Membership: Halbert-Hall, 1907-1995 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Membership: Hall-Hardin, 1910-1988 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Membership: Hardin-Harrison, 1900-1923 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Membership: Harston-Hayward, 1909-1990 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Membership: Hefley-Hiles, 1908-1981 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Membership: Hill-Hines, 1974-1989 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Membership: Holden-Horner, 1938-1978 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Membership: Horsfull-Howell, 1906-1998 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Membership: Howell, 1971-1977 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Membership: Hughes, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Membership: Hunt-Hunter, 1970-1980 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Membership: Irving, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Membership: Jackson-Johnson, 1916-1991 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Membership: Johnson, 1907-1971 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Membership: Johnston-Josephs, 1909-1979 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Membership: Kately-Kemp, 1917-1988 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Membership: Kendall-Kennedy, 1907-1990 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Membership: Kethley-Koss, 1919-1996 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Membership: Lacy-Lawrence, 1907-1982 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Membership: Lawson-Lea, 1964-1981 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Membership: Leal-Leonard, 1901-1998 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Membership: Lester-Libhart, 1934-1993 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Membership: Lindenberger-Linville, 1977-1980 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Membership: Little-Longfield, 1911-1989 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Membership: Lowe-Lutz, 1944-1991 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Membership: MacArthur-Mangum, 1942-2003 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Membership: Mangum-Maroski, 1907-1986 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Membership: Marshall-Masters, 1898-1988 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Membership: Mather-Maxwell, 1914-1978 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Membership: Mayer, 1976-1982 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Membership: Mayfield-McCall, 1917-1980 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Membership: McCammon-McCormick, 1968-1983 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Membership: McCormick-McCullough, 1909-1982 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Membership: McCune-McElhannon, 1973-1989 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Membership: McEntire-McGregor, 1922-1987 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Membership: McIntosh-McLaughlin, 1974-2001 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Membership: McLaughlin-McReynolds, 1946-1983 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Membership: McSwain, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Membership: Mehaffey-Meroney, 1968-1992 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Membership: Meter-Mills, 1922-1981 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Membership: Mims-Mitchell, 1975-1997 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Membership: Monfort-Monschke, 1975-1997 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Membership: Montgomery, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Membership: Moore-Morgan, 1910-1981 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Membership: Morgan-Morrow, 1903-1979 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Membership: Morton-Mullan, 1969-2001 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Membership: Murphy, 1979-1989 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Membership: Neale-Newton, 1908-1970 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Membership: Nichols-Norcross, 1923-1998 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Membership: Norwood, 1915-1995 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Membership: O’Brien-Oliver, 1926-1995 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Membership: Olsen-Oxner, 1909-2001 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Membership: Padgett-Parmelee, 1922-1990 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Membership: Patlack-Peele, 1944-1981 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Membership: Peeples-Pitzer, 1969-2001 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Membership: Pogue-Potts, 1921-1998 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Membership: Powell-Prather, 1907-1981 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Membership: Presley-Pruett, 1921-1991 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Membership: Quicksall-Quinius, 1934-1944 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Membership: Reaves-Reid, 1926-1994 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Membership: Reyer-Ricks, 1916-1998 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Membership: Riddle-Robertson, 1907-2002 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Membership: Rochell-Rountree, 1901-1982 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Membership: Rowland-Rudolph, 1973-1997 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Membership: Ruggiero-Ryle, 1935-1995 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Membership: Sanderlin-Schieffer, 1909-2002 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Membership: Schieffer-Scott, 1981-1987 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Membership: Scott-Sherman, 1902-1981 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Membership: Shields-Slade, 1931-1987 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Membership: Slade-Smith, 1916-1996 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Membership: Smith, 1911-1978 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Membership: Smith-Soules, 1910-1990 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Membership: Spencer-Stanford, 1910-1991 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Membership: Stanford-Stearns, 1924-1981 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Membership: Stern-Stewart, 1923-1993 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Membership: Stewart-Stone, 1978-1990 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Membership: Story-Sullivan, 1898-1997 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Membership: Summerhays-Symes, 1919-1976 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Membership: Talbert-Tate, 1926-1975 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Membership: Taylor-Thompson, 1922-1996 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Membership: Thornberg-Tinsley, 1976-1981 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Membership: Tilton-Trippett, 1906-1987 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Membership: Turner-Tuttle, 1901-1998 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Membership: Vansuch-Vivrett, 1946-1989 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Membership: Waddell-Walker, 1962-1984 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Membership: Walker, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Membership: Walker-Webb, 1926-1990 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Membership: Webb-West, 1900-1982 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Membership: Westbrook-White, 1902-1976 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Membership: White-Wiethorn, 1921-1989 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Membership: Wieting-Williams, 1925-1987 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Membership: Williams-Willis, 1913-1981 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Membership: Willis, 1917-1980 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Membership: Willis-Wilson, 1922-1982 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Membership: Wilson, 1925-1994 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Membership: Wilson-Witt, 1924-1989 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Membership: Wolff-Woodlock, 1936-1993 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Membership: Woodman-Wyche, 1944-2003 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Membership: Yantis-Young, 1917-1979 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Membership: Young-Youngblood, 1967-1999 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Literary Productions, 1900-2001; 5
  The following series contains literary productions produced by and for the Henry Downs Chapter of the American Revolution. Materials include handbooks, notes, clippings, by-laws, programs, reports, and other printed works. The bulk of the series is comprised of student essays composed for annual writing contests organized by the chapter. The series is in good condition.
  - By-Laws: National Society Daughters of the American Revolution, 1900, 1908 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - By-Laws: Henry Downs Chapter, undated (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - List: Deceased Members, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - List: Members: Henry Downs Chapter, undated (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Constitution and By-Laws: National Society Daughters of the American Revolution, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Histories: Henry Downs Chapter, 1929, 1975, undated (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Proclamation: Constitution Week, 1982, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Proclamation: Constitution Week, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Directory: Daughters of the American Revolution Committees, 1983-1984 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Certificates: Henry Downs Chapter, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Certificates: Writing Contest, undated (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Articles: Fay McClintock: Publicity, 1977 March-September (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Articles: Fay McClintock: Publicity, 1977 October-1978 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Manual: For the Information of Immigrants and Foreigners, 1930 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Manual: Is That Lineage Right?, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Pamphlet: “General Information and Requirements for and Preparation of Application Papers”, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Pamphlet: “Information for Chapter Registrars”, undated (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Pamphlet: “Promoting and Conserving our Chapters”, undated (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Brochure: Katie Duncan Smith D.A.R. School, circa 1999 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Brochure: “Marked for Posterity”, circa 1929 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Devotionals: Chaplains: National Society Daughters of the American Revolution, 1965-1968 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Devotionals: Chaplains: National Society Daughters of the American Revolution, 1971-1974 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Devotionals: Chaplains: National Society Daughters of the American Revolution, 1974-1977 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Membership Roll: Henry Downs Chapter, 1959 November (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Membership Roll: Henry Downs Chapter, 1960-1963 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Membership Roll: Henry Downs Chapter, 1964-1965 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Membership Roll: Henry Downs Chapter: (1 of 2), undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Membership Roll: Henry Downs Chapter: (2 of 2), undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Guest Book: Henry Downs Chapter, 1901-1961 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Guest Book: Henry Downs Chapter, 1976-1984 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Handbook: Girl Home Makers Committee, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Handbook: Heart of Texas Regional History Fair, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Handbook: National Society Daughters of the American Revolution, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Handbook: National Society Daughters of the American Revolution, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Clippings: General, 1985-1999, undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Clippings: Feature Series Contest, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Clippings: Public Relations Committee: (1 of 2), 1976 March-1977 February (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Clippings: Public Relations Committee: (2 of 2), 1976 March-1977 February (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Clippings: Public Relations Committee, 1977 March-1978 February (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Clippings: Public Relations Committee, 1978 March-1979 February (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Press Book: Clippings, 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Bible Records: Henry Downs Chapter: (1 of 5), 1985 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Bible Records: Henry Downs Chapter: (2 of 5), 1985 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Bible Records: Henry Downs Chapter: (3 of 5), 1985 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Bible Records: Henry Downs Chapter: (4 of 5), 1985 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Bible Records: Henry Downs Chapter: (5 of 5), 1985 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Book: Registrar: Henry Downs Chapter, 1906-1922 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Notebook: Chaplain: Henry Downs Chapters: (1 of 3), 1976-1984 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Notebook: Chaplain: Henry Downs Chapters: (2 of 3), 1976-1984 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Notebook: Chaplain: Henry Downs Chapters: (3 of 3), 1976-1984 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Notebook: Chaplain: Henry Downs Chapters: (1 of 2), 1984-1988 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Notebook: Chaplain: Henry Downs Chapters: (2 of 2), 1984-1988 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Notebook: Chaplain: Henry Downs Chapters: (1 of 2), 1988-1998 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Notebook: Chaplain: Henry Downs Chapters: (2 of 2), 1988-1998 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Bulletin: Texas Society Daughters of the American Revolution, 1960 October-1963 February (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Bulletin: Texas Society Daughters of the American Revolution, 1963 Fall-1967 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Bulletin: Texas Society Daughters of the American Revolution, 1968-1969 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Bulletin: Texas Society Daughters of the American Revolution, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Bulletin: Texas Society Daughters of the American Revolution, 1972-1973 June (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Bulletin: Texas Society Daughters of the American Revolution, 1973 September-1974 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Bulletin: Texas Society Daughters of the American Revolution, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Bulletin: Texas Society Daughters of the American Revolution, 1977 Spring (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Bulletin: Texas Society Daughters of the American Revolution, 1978-1979 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Bulletin: Texas Society Daughters of the American Revolution, 1980-1981 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Bulletin: Texas Society Daughters of the American Revolution, 1984 Fall (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Reports: Registrar’s Book: Henry Downs Chapter: (1 of 8), 1922-1948 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Reports: Registrar’s Book: Henry Downs Chapter: (2 of 8), 1922-1948 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Reports: Registrar’s Book: Henry Downs Chapter: (3 of 8), 1922-1948 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Reports: Registrar’s Book: Henry Downs Chapter: (4 of 8), 1922-1948 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Reports: Registrar’s Book: Henry Downs Chapter (5 of 8), 1922-1948 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Reports: Registrar’s Book: Henry Downs Chapter (6 of 8), 1922-1948 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Reports: Registrar’s Book: Henry Downs Chapter (7 of 8), 1922-1948 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Reports: Registrar’s Book: Henry Downs Chapter (8 of 8), 1922-1948 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Reports: Registrar’s Book: Henry Downs Chapter (1 of 5), 1948-1961 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Reports: Registrar’s Book: Henry Downs Chapter (2 of 5), 1948-1961 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Reports: Registrar’s Book: Henry Downs Chapter (3 of 5), 1948-1961 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Reports: Registrar’s Book: Henry Downs Chapter (4 of 5), 1948-1961 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Reports: Registrar’s Book: Henry Downs Chapter (5 of 5), 1948-1961 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Reports: Registrar’s Book: Henry Downs Chapter, 1961-1967 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Printed Materials: General, 1968-1974 September (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Printed Materials: General, 1974 October-1975 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Printed Materials: General, 1976-1981 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Printed Materials: General, 1982-1998 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Printed Materials: General (1 of 4), undated (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Printed Materials: General (2 of 4), undated (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Printed Materials: General (3 of 4), undated (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Printed Materials: General (4 of 4), undated (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Ninetieth Anniversary: Henry Downs Chapter (1 of 3), 1991 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Printed Materials: Ninetieth Anniversary: Henry Downs Chapter (2 of 3), 1991 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Printed Materials: Ninetieth Anniversary: Henry Downs Chapter (3 of 3), 1991 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Printed Materials: Celebrations: General, 1947-1969 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Printed Materials: Celebrations: General, 1971-1990, undated (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Printed Materials: Chaplains: (1 of 2), 1996-1998, undated (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Printed Materials: Chaplains: (2 of 2), 1996-1998, undated (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Printed Materials: Entertainment Committee, 1957-1963 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Printed Materials: Entertainment Committee, 1964, undated (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Printed Materials: Essay Contest: Henry Downs Chapter, 1980-1985 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Printed Materials: Grave Markers, 1980-1990 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Printed Materials: KAWA Radio Station (1 of 4), 1961-1963 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Literary Productions: Printed Materials: KAWA Radio Station (2 of 4), 1961-1963 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Printed Materials: KAWA Radio Station (3 of 4), 1961-1963 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Printed Materials: KAWA Radio Station (4 of 4), 1961-1963 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Printed Materials: National Defense Committee, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Printed Materials: Recording Secretaries, 1981-1989, undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Printed Materials: Texan Ethnic Cuisine, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Notes: Fay McClintock: Publicity, 1976 September-1977 February (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Notes: Henry Downs, 1901-1981, undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Notes: Nuclear Program, 1981 March 6 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Notes: Obituaries, 1982-1984, undated (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Notes: Regents: Henry Downs Chapter (1 of 3), 1982 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Notes: Regents: Henry Downs Chapter (2 of 3), 1982 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Notes: Regents: Henry Downs Chapter (3 of 3), 1982 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Notes: Thirty-First Annual Conference: Texas Society Daughters of the American Revolution, 1930 November 3-6 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Notes: Children of Revolutionary Ancestors: “A”, undated (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Children of Revolutionary Ancestors: “B”, undated (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Notes: Children of Revolutionary Ancestors: “C”, undated (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Notes: Children of Revolutionary Ancestors: “D” and “E”, undated (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Notes: Children of Revolutionary Ancestors: “F” and “G”, undated (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Notes: Children of Revolutionary Ancestors: “H”, undated (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Notes: Children of Revolutionary Ancestors: “J”, “K”, and “L”, undated (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Notes: Children of Revolutionary Ancestors: “M”, undated (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Notes: Children of Revolutionary Ancestors: “N”, “O”, and “P”, undated (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Notes: Children of Revolutionary Ancestors: “R”, undated (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Notes: Children of Revolutionary Ancestors: “S”, undated (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Notes: Children of Revolutionary Ancestors: “T” and “V”, undated (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Notes: Children of Revolutionary Ancestors: “W” and “Y”, undated (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Program: Centennial Celebration, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Program: Volunteer Recognition Dinner, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Program: “What the Daughters Do”, 1929-1930, 1932-1933 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Program: Thirty-Ninth Annual Conference: National Society Daughters of the American Revolution, 1938 March 16-19 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Program: Seventy-Second and Seventy-Eighth Continental Congresses: National Society Daughters of the American Revolution, 1963, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Program: Eightieth Continental Congress: National Society Daughters of the American Revolution, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Program: Eighty-First Continental Congress: National Society Daughters of the American Revolution, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Program: Eighty-Second Continental Congress: National Society Daughters of the American Revolution, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 35)